Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - Side A: Walsh, Jim, "Ireland In My Dreams" Side B: Walsh, Jim, "Those Endearing Young Charms", 1986 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Streets of New York" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "The Connaught Ranger", 1981 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: MacEwan, Sydney, "Suffer Little Children" Side B: MacEwan, Sydney, "Our Father", 1972 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Grace, Brendan, "Liberty Boy" Side B: Grace, Brendan, "Industrial Fair", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Kingston, Noel, "I Am Joe Cahill" Side B: Kingston, Noel, "Gradh Mo Chroi", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: McCaffrey, Frank, "Lough Sheelin" Side B: McCaffrey, Frank, "Faded Love", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: The Chieftains, "The Love Theme from Barry Lyndon (Women of Ireland)" Side B: The Chieftains, "The Timpan Reel", 1975 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Anthony, Brian, "Ireland United Gaelic and Free" Side B: Anthony, Brian, "Kevin Barry", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Uncle Nobby's Steamboat" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "God Save Ireland", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Margo & Co, "Shamrock From Glenore" and "Bonny Scotland" Side B: Margo & Co, "Cliffs of Dooneen" and "Road & The Miles To Dundee", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Kelly, Stan, "The Ballad Of Armagh Jail" Side B: Kelly, Stan, "Kelly The Boy From Killane", 1970 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Byrne, Kenny, "Boolavogue" Side B: Hickey, Bill, "Medley Of Irish Jigs", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: Margo & The Keynotes, "Bonny Irish Boy" Side B: Margo & The Keynotes, "Dear God", 1968 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Where Is The Summertime?" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "He Walks Like You", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat, "It's The Ring Your Mother Wore" Side B: Lynch, Pat, "I'll Take You Where The Music's Playing", 1968 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: The Saints Showband, "The Broken Hearted Farmer" Side B: The Saints Showband, "The Old Bog Road", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Wonderful World Of My Dreams" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "The Worst Mistake", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Murray, Ruby, "The Little Pine Tree" Side B: Murray, Ruby, "Silent Night", 1965 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Trinity, "When Will I Be Loved" Side B: Trinity, "Love Song", 1975 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: McEvoy, Johnny, "Rose Of Allendale" Side B: McEvoy, Johnny, "Life Of The Rover", 1975 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "The Emerald Isle Express" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "Gweevara Bay", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Fleming, Sean, and Ebneth, Chris, "Streets Of London" Side B: Fleming, Sean, and Ebneth, Chris, "The Battle Of New Orleans", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: Drennan, Tommy, "December Song" Side B: Drennan, Tommy, "Beautiful Peace", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: The Black Water Boys, "The Band Played Waltzing Matilda" Side B: The Black Water Boys, "Drunken' Sailor", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "It's Heaven Around Galway Bay" and "Come Back Home To Erin" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "In The Corner Of My Prison Cell" and "Connemara Lullaby", 1961 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Mac, Billy, "My Dublin Bay" Side B: Mac, Billy, "Help Me Make It Thro' The Night", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "The Shores of Amerikay" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "The Wild Colonial Boy", 1967 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Up And Away (The Helicopter Song)" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "The Broad Black Brimmer", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Snowflake" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "The Wild Rapparee", 1966 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Side A: Grace, Brendan, "Long Before Your Time" Side B: Grace, Brendan, "My Heart Is In Ireland", 1985 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Side A: Chilton Books, "Lesson 31" Side B: Chilton Books, "Lesson 32", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Shine, Brendan, "I Believe In Marriage" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Connolly, Mary, "Come Back Home to Erin" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - The Ramblers Two, "Come to the Bower" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 71)
    - Doris, Malachy and his Band, "Irish Jigs" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 72)
    - The Wolf Tones, "The Teddy Bear's Head" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 73)
    - Dooley, Maisie, "Music of Ireland" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 74)
    - Tomelty, Peter, "That's How I Spell Ireland" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 75)
    - Mac, Billy, "My Dublin Bay", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 76)
    - Connolly, Mary, "Come Back Home to Erin" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 77)
    - Trinity, "When Will I Be Loved" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 78)
    - Side A: The Ramblers, "Come to the Bower" and "God Save Ireland" Side B: The Ramblers, "The West's Asleep" and "The Bold Fenian Men", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Bree, Barley, "Windmills" Side B: Bree, Barley, "Jigs: The Tulla Jig, Etc.", 1977 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Connolly, Mary, "It's Heaven Around Galway Bay" and "Come Back Home to Erin" Side B: Connolly, Mary, "In the Corner of My Prison Cell" and "Connemara Lullaby", 1961 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Driscoll, Jack, "Bobby Sands" Side B: Traditional, "Spancil Hill", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "I Believe in Marriage" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "It's Good to See You", 1981 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Curran, Cyril, "Treat Me Daughter Kindly" Side B: Kenny, Charles and Nick, "Cathedral in the Pines", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Rose Tree" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Cuckoo Waltz", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Brady, Willie, "Finnigan's Ball" Side B: Brady, Willie, "Paddy McGinty's Goat", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: The Bankers Showband, "The Old Boreen" Side B: The Bankers Showband, "Lovely Leenan Bay", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael & Sons, "Love is Teasin'" Side B: O'Duffy, Micahel & Sons, "Scarlet Ribbons", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Foley, Connie, "Home of Donegal" Side B: Foley, Connie, "Boys from the County Armagh", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Hughes, Anthony & the Ventures, "Little Girl" Side B: Hughes, Anthony & the Ventures, "If A Woman Answers", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "If You're Lonesome at Your Table" Side B: Big Tom and the Mainliners, "An Old Log Cabin for Sale", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Jerry, "The Shannon" Side B: O'Brien, Jerry, "The Gal in Old Mayo", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: McDermott, Francis, "The Irish Way to Love" Side B: McDermott, Francis, "Chasing the Rainbow", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: McGarr, Jimmy and the Gallowglass, "The Boys from the County Cork" Side B: McGarr, Jimmy and the Gallowglass, "On the One Road", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: The Johnny Flynn Sound featuring Peter Creighton, "Banna Strand" Side B: The Johnny Flynn Sound featuring Frankie Hannon, "Heart Break Hill", 1970 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "My Ireland" Side B: McGonigle, Mary, "Leprechaun", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Catch Me If You Can" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Coastline of Mayo", 1980 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: Logan, Al, "The Wedding" Side B: Logan, Al, "St. Therese of the Roses", 1977 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: The Irish Tradewinds, "Ireland United" Side B: The Irish Tradewinds, "The Boys in the Old Brigade", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: The Tinkers, "The Rising of the Moon" Side B: The Tinkers, "Tell Ireland I Still Miss Her", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Doonaree" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "Laois and Offaly", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Supple, Art and the Victors, "The Boys of Kilmichael" Side B: Supple, Art and the Victors, "Big Chief Buffalo Nickel", 1969 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Frawley, Eileen, "Ireland's 32" Side B: Frawley, Eileen, "One Day at a Time", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Birdie, "Teddy O'Neale" and "Ballyhoe" Side B: Gallagher, Birdie, "Irish Soldier Boy" and "Shall My Soul Pass Through Old Ireland", 1960 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: The Dubliners, "Nelson's Farewell" Side B: The Dubliners, "The Foggy Dew", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Penny & the Skyrockets, "Noreen Bawn" Side B: Penny & the Skyrockets, "After the Dance", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Moore, Christy, "Ninety Miles from Dublin Town" Side B: Traditional, "The Rights of Man. Repeal the Union", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Byrne, Kenny, "Boolavogue" Side B: Hickey, Bill and his Orchestra, "Medley of Irish Jigs", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: The Celtic Flavor, "A Long Way From Clare to Here" Side B: The Celtic Flavor, "Let Mr. McGuire Sit Down", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Just Rodgers & Basic Pay, "Ballyheigue Bay" Side B: Just Rodgers & Basic Pay, "My Beautiful Green Fields", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Norry, Nita, "I'll Rememeber You Love In My Prayers" Side B: Noory, Nita, "The Wild Colonial Boy", 1971 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Owens, Michael "Jesse," "Saturday Night in Dublin" Side B: Owens, Michael "Jesse," "Come With Me Molly", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: The Wild Colonial Boys, "Bobby Sands Side B: The Wild Colonial Boys, "Spancil Hill", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "Spancil Hill" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "Slieve Gallion Braes", 1974 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: McBride, Frank, and the Polka Dots, "The Blackboard of my Heart" Side B: McBride, Frank, and the Polka Dots, "A Cottage in Old Donegal", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Faughan Side" and "Lady Colleen" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Co. Leitrim Queen" and "Beggar Man", 1978 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "The Whistling Gypsy" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Two Rivers", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "The Mucky Kid" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "Gone Away", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Carlton, Clipper, "A Little Bit of Me Dies" Side B: Carlton, Clipper, "The March Hare", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "When the Fields are White with Daisies" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "What Am I Doing Hangin' Round?", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Tomelty, Peter, "The Irish Patrol" Side B: Tomelty, Peter, "The Ballad of Jack Kennedy", 1961 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: The Gaspar Netscher Ensemble, "Get Out of Bed My Darling" Side B: The Gaspar Netscher Ensemble, "Until You're Here Beside Me", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: Gael-Linn Ceolta Eireann, "Bhio-sa la I bPort Lairge" Side B: Gael-Linn Ceolta Eireann, "An Chuilfhionn", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Murphy, Johnny, "Lough Sheelin" Side B: Murphy, Johnny, "I Still Miss Someone", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Colm, "The Right Honourable Bobby Sands" Side B: Gallagher, Colm, "If I Could Talk to Francis Hughes", 1981 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Mulhare, Martin, "The Sheep in the Meadow and the Cat in the Corner" Side B: Mulhare, Martin, "O'Brien's Reel and the Yellow Tinker", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "The Irish Soldier" Side B: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "Big Job", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Four Hand Reel" and "An Siamsa Bierte" Side B: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Eight Hand Reel" and "Pride of Erin Waltz", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Kerr, James, "Irish Washerwoman. Medley of Jigs: Irish Washerwoman. Father O'Flynn. Donnybrook Boy" Side B: Kerr, James, "Pride of Erin Waltz. Eillean Allanah Oft in the Stilly Night The Gentle Maiden", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Kings Dreamer, "Beautiful Dreamer" Side B: Kings Showband, "I Fall to Pieces", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Derrick & the Sounds, "Power of Love" Side B: Derrick & the Sounds, "I'll Take You Home", 1968 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: O'Dowd, Mary, "Jackets Green" Side B: O'Dowd, Mary, "Bonie Wee Lad", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Duncan, Hugo and the Tall Men, "Three Leaf Shamrock" Side B: Duncan, Hugo and the Tall Men, "Poplar Bluff", 1972 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: The Rambler (John McEvoy), "Muirsheen Durkin" Side B: The Rambler (John McEvoy), "Those Brown Eyes", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Long Island Dallas Defense (L.I.L.L.), "Saoirse" and "The Fortworth Five" Side B: Side A: Long Island Dallas Defense (L.I.L.L.), "Saoirse" and "The Boys of the Old Brigade", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian and the Plattermen, "The Blazing Star of Athenry" Side B: Coll, Brian and the Plattermen, "On the Banks of my Own Lovely Lee", 1966 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: Jesse & Arnold, "All Kinds of Everything" Side B: Jesse & Arnold, "Leaving London", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Show Me the Road to Ireland" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "Town of Galway", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael, "The Kerry Dance" and "Kitty Magee" Side B: O'Duffy, Michael, "Little Town in Cold County Down" and "Because I Love You So", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Jerry, "Ooh-Ooh-Ooh" Side B: O'Brien, Jerry, "The Ringing Bell", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Birdie, "Cottage on the Borderline" Side B: Gallagher, Birdie, "Rose of Mooncoin", 1967 (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: MacEwan, Father Sidney, "Terence's Farewell to Kathleen" and "Down by the Sally Gardens" Side B: MacEwan, Father Sidney, "The Short Cut to the Rosses" and "Fairy Story by the Fire", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Side A: Stewart, Andy, "A Scottish Soldier (Green Hills of Tyroll) Side B: Stewart, Andy, "The Muckin 'O' Geordie's Byre", undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - O'Brien, Jerry, "Ooh-Ooh-Ooh" and "The Ringing Bell" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "Dancing Round Ireland, Part 5" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - Norry, Nita, "I'll Remember You Love in My Prayers" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Se, Sean O, "Taimse im' Chodladh (The Boys of Kilmichael)" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Hegarty, Dermot, "The Faughan Side" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - O'Brien, Dermot, "Spancil Hill" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 71)
    - Gallagher, Birdie, "Irish Soldier Boy" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 72)
    - Daly, Pat and Paddy Noonan, "Delightful Irish Music & Song" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 34, Sound disc--vinyl 73)
    - Side A: Ivy Folk, "Ballad Brew" Side B: Ivy Folk, "Daydreamer", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: MaGuire, Brendan, "A Nation Once Again" Side B: MaGuire, Brendan, "Do You Want Your Old Lobby Washed Down", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Kingston, Noel, "Love Thee Dearest" and "The Village that Nobody Knows" Side B: Kingston, Noel, "Because I Love You So Machree" and "Bless This House", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "The Irish Soldier" Side B: Lynch, Pat & the Airchords, "Big Job", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: The Irish Blazers, " The Martyr from Mayo" Side B: Side B: The Irish Blazers, " An Irish Martyr", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: O'Duffy, Michael & Sons, "Love is Teasin'" Side B: O'Duffy, Micahel & Sons, "Scarlet Ribbons", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "If I Could Choose" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "Yellow Bandana", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Maguire, Sean, "Reels" Side B: Maguire, Sean, "Hornpipes", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Brolly, Anne & Francie, "Mass Rock in the Glen" Side B: Brolly, Anne & Francie, "Along the Faughan Side", 1970 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot and his Clubmen, "The Merry Ploughboy" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot and his Clubmen, "Come Down the Mountain Katie Daly", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "Lonely Woods of Upton" Side B: Dunphy, Sean and the Hoedowners, "Yellow Haired Woman", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Stewart, Andy, "A Scottish Soldier (Green Hills of Tyroll) Side B: Stewart, Andy, "The Muckin 'O' Geordie's Byre", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Trottin' to the Fair" and "Song of the Backwoods" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "Ballyshannon" and "My Lagan Love", 1959 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Barleycorn, "Bring Them Home" Side B: Barleycorn, "The Boys of the Old Brigade", 1974 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Dunlaoire" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Boyle in the Co. Roscommon", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Doyle, Danny, "Daisy A Day" Side B: Doyle, Danny, "Far Away In Australia", 1978 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Christmas Time in Ireland" Side B: Shine, Brendn, "Country Churchyard", 1974 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: The Irish Blazers, "The Old Stone Bridge" Side B: The Irish Blazers, "The Little White House", 1976 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Day, Paddy, "The Prisoner" Side B: Day, Paddy, "Dingle Bay", 1969 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Pageant at Knappogue Castle, 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: Noonan, Paddy and his band, "Glorious Green" Side B: Noonan, Paddy and his band, "Irish Coffee", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: The Irish Rovers, "The Unicorn" Side B: The Irish Rovers, "Black Velvet Band", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: The Irish Blazers, "The Old Stone Bridge" Side B: The Irish Blazers, "The Little White House", 1976 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Morgan, Ginger and the Mainliners, "Thinking of You" Side B: Morgan, Ginger and the Mainliners, "Gentle Mother:", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Mac, Dermie, "Born to Be With You" Side B: Mac, Dermie, "I Can't Go Back to Boston", 1976 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Margo and the Country Folk, "Gradh Mo Chroi" Side B: Margo and the Country Folk, "Mama, Say A Prayer", 1970 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Corrigan, Ian and Country Style, "County Cavan" Side B: Corrigan, Ian and Country Style, "In the Springtime", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Makem, Tommy, "Winds Are Singing Freedom" Side B: Makem, Tommy, "Lords of the Dance", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: The Beggar's Purse, "Beneath A Single Banner" Side B: The Beggar's Purse, "Rossville 13", 1972 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: Lynch, Joe, "Homes of Donegal" Side B: Lynch, Joe, "Delaney's Donkey", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: McBride, "Big" Tom and the Mainliners, "Gentle Mother" Side B: Morgan, Ginger and the Mainliners, "Thinking of You", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Donnolly, Seamus, "West of the Old River Shannon" Side B: Donnolly, Seamus, "McCarthy's Party", 1972 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Henry, Noel, "Peace on Erin's Green Shore" Side B: Henry, Noel, "Lambs in the Green Fields", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: McGee/Noonan, "Five Hundred Years" Side B: McCall, P.J., "Kelly from Killane", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "Cottage on the Borderline" Side B: Cunningham, Larry and the Mighty Avons, "Three Steps to the Phone", 1967 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Galway Shawl" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Flying Scotsman" and "The Turfman from Ardee", 1971 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Boys of Killybegs" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "As I Roved Out", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat with Paddy Noonan's Band, "Gentle Mother" Side B: Noonan, Paddy, "Irish Reel's", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot & the Clubmen, "The Rocks of Bawn" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot & the Clubmen, "Shufflin' Sam", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: Sweeneys Men, "Old Woman in Cotton" Side B: Sweeneys Men, "Waxies Dargle", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: Ruane Jr., Jack, "What About the Last Time" Side B: Ruane Jr., Jack, "The River Moy", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Margo, "West of the Old River Shannon" Side B: Margo, "I Wonder How The Old Folks Are at Home", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: Kenny, Tony, "I'll Have To Say I Love You In A Song" Side B: Kenny, Tony, "Close Every Door", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot and the Plainsmen, "Twenty One Year" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot and the Plainsmen, "Sing Me Back Home", 1970 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A & B: Maguire, Sean "Reels", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Coll, Brian and the Plattermen, "The Blazing Star of Athenry" Side B: Coll, Brian and the Plattermen, "On the Banks of my Own Lovely Lee", 1966 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Maguire, Sean, "Reels" Side B: Maguire, Sean, "Jigs", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: McEldowney, Eugene, "White, Organe, & Green" Side B: McEldowney, Eugene, "Ireland's Fight for Freedom", 1968 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: Raparees, "God Save Ireland" Side B: The Raparees, "Butcher Boy", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: Cash, Johnny, "Forty Shades of Green" Side B: Cash, Johnny, "The Rebel - Johnny Yuma", undated (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Barley Corn, "Men Behind the Wire" Side B: Barley Corn, "Freedom Walk", 1971 (Box 35, Sound disc--vinyl 51)